<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bandung Bermartabat</string>
    <string name="place_header_placeholder_text">Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia</string>
    <string name="place_info_placeholder_text">Kampus Pendidikan Nomor Satu di Bandung</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="taman_jomblo_info">This park built for every single person out there to hangout.</string>
    <string name="tangkubanperahu_info">Very famous mountain with beautiful legend. Must visit place if you spent holiday in Bandung.</string>
    <string name="tangkubanperahu_header">Tangkuban Perahu</string>
    <string name="situpatenggang_header">Situ Patenggang</string>
    <string name="situpatenggang_info">This beautiful lake is enormous. You could get beautiful sunrise here.</string>
    <string name="museumgeologi_header">Museum Geologi</string>
    <string name="museumgeologi_info">He you could find a mammoth fossil, earthquake simulator, history on origin of Bandung, etc..</string>
    <string name="ciwidey_header">Ciwidey</string>
    <string name="ciwidey_info">This place is so touching if you visit with your beloved. Remember, don\'t come alone!</string>
    <string name="dago_header">Dago Waterfall</string>
    <string name="dago_info">It\'s not as big as Niagara Waterfall, but it\'s unique. It\'s uniqueness comes from the place where it place. If you think waterfall are placed so far away from the city, you would surprised when visiting this waterfall.</string>
    <string name="alfurqon_header">Al-Furqon UPI</string>
    <string name="alfurqon_info">This is the official mosque for Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia. The biggest on campus mosque.</string>
    <string name="salman_header">Salman ITB</string>
    <string name="salman_info">This is where the future engineer of Indonesia take a rest and pray to God in ITB.</string>
    <string name="masjidraya_header">Masjid Raya</string>
    <string name="masjidraya_info">This one is the biggest mosque in Bandung and one of Bandung\'s landmark.</string>
    <string name="pusdai_header">Masjid Pusdai</string>
    <string name="pusdai_info">This mosque is where the center of Islamic in Bandung takes place.</string>
    <string name="ciater_header">Masjid Agung Ciater</string>
    <string name="ciater_info">People who visited hot spring in Ciater would pray in this mosque.</string>
    <string name="tamanfilm_header">Taman Film</string>
    <string name="tamanvanda_header">Taman Vanda</string>
    <string name="tamanmusik_header">Taman Musik</string>
    <string name="tamanfoto_header">Taman Foto</string>
    <string name="tamanlansia_header">Taman Lansia</string>
    <string name="tamanfilm_info">This park is built for Bandung citizen so they could watch movies together.</string>
    <string name="tamanvanda_info">This park is built near the Bank Indonesia, the national bank of Indonesia which have beautiful water.</string>
    <string name="tamanmusik_info">This park is built to accomodate musician that looking for place to find inspiration.</string>
    <string name="tamanfoto_info">This park is built to help people of Bandung to learn photography.</string>
    <string name="tamanlansia_info">This park is built for elder so they have a place to hangout safely</string>
    <string name="itb_header">Institut Teknologi Bandung</string>
    <string name="upi_header">Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia</string>
    <string name="unpad_header">Universitas Padjajaran</string>
    <string name="polban_header">Politeknik Negeri Bandung</string>
    <string name="telkom_header">Telkom University</string>
    <string name="itb_info">This institute is the most prestigious in technical education. Famous with its Informatics Engineering Department.</string>
    <string name="upi_info">Leading and outstanding university in the field of education. Produce high quality teacher to bring better future.</string>
    <string name="unpad_info">Another prestigious university in Bandung. Unpad famous with it\'s social studies.</string>
    <string name="polban_info">The state owned polytechnic is very famous among student who want to get job fast.</string>
    <string name="telkom_info">Owned by the biggest Telecom Company in Indonesia.</string>
</resources>
